{
    "subject": "resource/Society_of_Jesus",
    "predicate": "ontology/location",
    "object": "resource/Rome",
    "human_readable": "The location of the Society of Jesus is Rome.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8089274764060974,
            "question": "Where is the Society of Jesus located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6667010188102722,
            "question": "Is the Society of Jesus located in Europe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5859090685844421,
            "question": "What city is the headquarters of the Society of Jesus in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44571927189826965,
            "question": "In what country is the Society of Jesus based?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40551355481147766,
            "question": "Where can you find the main center of operations for the Society of Jesus?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38938093185424805,
            "question": "What is the location of the Society of Jesus' central offices?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3765530586242676,
            "question": "Name a significant religious organization headquartered in Rome."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2631053626537323,
            "question": "What religious order is associated with Rome?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2581939697265625,
            "question": "Rome is known for being the home to which religious group?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.05813483148813248,
            "question": "Which city houses the headquarters of a well-known Jesuit organization?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The location of the Society of Jesus is Rome.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7803_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Rome is known for being the home to which religious group?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7803_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What religious order is associated with Rome?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7803_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a significant religious organization headquartered in Rome.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7803_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7803_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7803_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7803_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7803_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7803_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7803_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7803_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7803_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7803_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7803_63.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the documents, the Society of Jesus was founded in Rome, Italy, and it has its global headquarters (Jesuit Curia) located in Rome. This supports the statement that the location of the Society of Jesus is indeed Rome."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents state that the Jesuit Curia, which serves as the headquarters of the Society of Jesus, is located in Rome. Therefore, the statement \"The location of the Society of Jesus is Rome\" is supported by the given context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}